Guide to the Mark Kulstad Academic Papers, 1971-2015 UA 385
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Professional Development, 1981-2014 (Box 4-11)
  - Lectures and Conferences, 1998-2016 (Box 9-11)
    - To be presented at Fourth International Leibniz Congress Leibniz's Theory of Innateness in the new essays followed by a few remarks on the possible impact on Kant (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Portland information + Descartes conference (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Notes on Memphis conference (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Lebiniz awards (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - VIII. Lebniz Kongress (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - International Young Leibniz Conference photos, 2003
    - Second Annual Leibniz Society of North America Conference photos, 2008-09
    - Inaugural Leibniz Society of North America Conference photos - 30th Annivesary of LSNA, 2008-01
    - Third Annual Leibniz Society of North America Conference photos (University of Kentucky), 2009
    - Fourth Annual Leibniz Society of North America Conference photos (University of Houston), 2010
    - Fifth Annual Leibniz Society of North America Conference photos (UC - San Diego), 2011
    - LSNA members at International Leibniz Congress in Hanover, Germany photos, 2016
    - International scholars at Hanover Leibniz Congress photos, 2016
    - Cover scans of LSNA linked publications
- Series III: Graduate Seminars and Admissions, 1984-2015 (Box 11-14)
  - Graduate Seminars and Admissions, 1984-2015 (Box 11-14)
    - 502, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - MAK: PHIL502- LK + Leibniz, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - 502 News, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - 502 SC + phil, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - 502 new essays, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - PHIL 502 "Greats", ca. 1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Phil 502 Sleigh, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - PHIL 502 Fall, Lebniz + Sp, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - 502, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - PHIL 502 Fall D-K Causation, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - PHIL 502 Sleigh + Adams, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - PHIL 502 Spring, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 502 Greats PHIL, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 502 readings marked copies, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 502 F. Grts, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Lebniz on LK on mathematical knowledge in the NE ( Submitted to HPQ, 2002) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - PHIL 502, Spr Greats, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New Essays PHIL 502, 2002-05 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - PHIL 502 Mogens, Laerke lectures, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Spinoza seminar readings (unmarked) Mason, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - PHIL 502 Fall? Leibniz and SP, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Readings for PHIL 502 wK 2. 502 Jack Dav Grts 2008 recommendations (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 502 Jack David Grts Lebniz power + freedom, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - PHIL 502 Greats w/ Jack Davidson, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Spinoza W/ Gregory Kaplan, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - PHIL 502 Theodicy, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - PHIL 502 LKLZ S Epist PHIL SC, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 502 Fall Garber, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 502 S pos, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - PHIL 502 F, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Philsophy of Language (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - PHIL 502 readings (already discussed) Greats D (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - PHIL 501a lecture and summaries (storage notes) (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Leibniz: De Summa Rerum (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - 502 "On the Origin of thg frm Forms" DSR PP. 76-83 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - PHIL 502 readings, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - PHIL 502 readings (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Loeb from Descartes to Hume" (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Garber, "Science & Certainty" (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Mason, R. "Spinoza on Modality" MAK marked copy (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Chas Jarrett "Log Struct of Sp's EI" MAK Marked copy (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - PHIL 502 Sleigh Papers PHIL 502 Mondadori (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Mates review of LA Mates vs. Sleighorn Lebniz + Arnauld PHIL 502 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Mondadori PHIL 502 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - McCracken: Malebrt + Hume on Cause (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Kulstad in Nadler PHIL 502 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - The Lebiniz Arnauld Correspondence PHIL 502 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - PHIL 502 readings/Causation (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Winkler, "The New Hume" modestly marked (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Short works of Leibniz (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - PHIL 502 Readings Spring Greats Phil Kulstad, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Locke Abstract of the Essay (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Malebranche: Dialogues marked up (MK) COPY (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Adams, Sleigh (2) (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Descartes (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Spinoza's D'spp (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Jack Davidson " LK'S Finely Spun Liberty" (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Loeb's Sp on Attrib and Mode PHIL 302 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Selections from Sp's D's prs (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - C. Wilson, Delpsa Natura (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Loeb: If D. is a Rat, so is LK...? (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Kant Eberhard RDGS ( And Allison Intro) (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Hume Treatise I Vii "Conclusion of the book" (good pts on sk + cause) Bennett volume (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Bennett Volume (Box 12, Folder 53-58)
    - Garrett PHIL 502 Spinoza Ethics I PSD (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - MK On Frankfurt on Descartes (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - "Once used" readings 502, L and SP (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Janet Braughton "Hume's ideas about necessary connection" (Jermy Dorset used it for critical paper) (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - 502 Leibniz Seminar, Leibniz draft and NE Science (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 502 SC + PHIL- Galileo- Newton; Descartes The World Cottingham pp. 79-98 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 502: SC + PHIL- Galileo- N, Gassendi Diss. inform of paradoxes R. popkin Philosophy of 16th and 17th century (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 502: Sc + PHIL- Galileo - N, L.Loeb from Descartes to Hume (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 502: SC + PHIL- Galileo- N, Leibniz Conference Against Atheists (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 502: SC + phil- Galileo- N, Garber " SC + Certainty in Descartes" (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 502: SC + PHIL- Galileo- N Garber Motion and Metaphysics in Young Lebniz Hooker: Lebniz Criteria and interpation essays (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Admissions final phone calls, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Admissions Spring, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Assignments + Faculty grades, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Admissions database revision Fall, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Mtl: assignments (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15,16)
    - Data sheets, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Department tasks (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Admissions Spring End Game, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Guidelines for Graduate study (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 3-8)
    - Graduate Admissions FAQ'S (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1998-2013 (Box 14, Folder 10-32)
    - Graduate Admissions, 2015 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Graduate Admissions related material (Box 14, Folder 34-40)
- Series IV: Course Material, 1975-2014 (Box 15-20)
  - MK PHIL 303, 1975-2001 (Box 15)
    - 303a Epistemology Storage (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - PHIL 303 Rdgs MAK Working copies (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - PHIL 303b Clean Readings Theory of Knowledge (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Syallabi, Tests, + study sheets 303a (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - PHIL 303a Epist. old lecture material (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - M. Kulstad PHIL 303a (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Course Articles (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - UG Epist, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Undergrad Epistomology, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 303a Epistomlogy UG, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 303A Class Nice Outlines, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Phil 303b Kulstad Quinton Foundations of Knowledge (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Phil 303a Dancy Spring, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 303a Papers (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 303a Study Sheet (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Phil 303 Keith Derose, Skepticism Seminar (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 303a Epist. Packets, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 303a Spring, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Humanities Course 101 1st Sem (Faculty meetings: summer + fall), 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - PHIL 303 Student's (Lu) Lecture notes Theory of Knowledge Spring, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - PHIL 303 Spring, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - HUMA 101 (1994- 1999) (Box 16)
    - HUMA 101 Lectures, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - HUMA 101 Record Keeping, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - HUMA 101 007 Fall RH 102, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - HUMA Meetings + Fall Faculty Sessions 101, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - HUMA 101 Fall, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - HUMA 101 Summer + Fall Sem, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - HUMA Summer Seminar 102 but also merged 101-102 + film, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Presentation on Republic HUMA 101 Fernando Casa + Mark Kulstad Fall, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - HUMA 101-102 Summer Workshop Freud and Einstein (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Job Eleanor Stump (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - HUMA 101: 2ndary lit for readings no longer used (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - FW15 111 2013, 2005-2013 (Box 16)
    - FW 15111 Presentations (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - FW15111 '13F (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Status of Women in Philosophy Hailey Hinson Writing Project, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - PHIL 302 (formerly 417) and grades for many courses and many years 202, 303 etc., 1975-2013 (Box 16)
    - 417/302 Cover packets (RAT), 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Dusty Capistran; 302b Storage Br. Empricists + Reid + Kant, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 302 EMP, 1978-2012 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - PHIL 302b Emp; Syallabi, etc. Class Outlines, 1982-1998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 302 EMP Final Exam Q's (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Tiumak's Handouts (Mod Phil- LZ Leibniz Society, etc.) (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - PHIL 302 RAT: Handouts (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 302 EMP Handouts (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 302 Photocopy Texts + Handouts (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - 302b Rat Lecture (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - PHIL 417a The Rationalist Tradition (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 302 Loebversion, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 302, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 302 Spring, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 302 Spring, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 302 Great Issues, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 302 Spring, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 302, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - HUME, 2011-11 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - PHIL 302 Spring, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - PHIL 302, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Lecture Notes on Spinoza 302, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - 302 Spring, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - PHIL 302 D.M,SP,LZ F, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - PHIL 302 Emps. Spring, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - PHIL 302 Spring RATS, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - PHIL 302 Spring, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - PHIL 302 RAT Fall, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - EMP PHIL 302 Fall, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - PHIL 302 F RATS, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - PHIL 302 EMP F, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 302 RATS, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Independent Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
    - Independent Studies; PHIL 402b Andrew Tucker Independent Study (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Independent Study, Raymond Ng, Ford, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Darren Lynx Independent Study 402 Sp (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Professor Kulstad (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - 503, 1976-1980 (Box 17)
    - Grad Epist. Storage 503 a lecture notes (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - PHIL 502a old lecture mtl (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - 503a Syallabi + lecture outlines, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - 503, Sem in Epist: Fall syallabus and roster, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Tlumak + Shuger (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 501a, 1977-1983 (Box 17)
    - Handouts, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 33,34)
    - Extra Lecture MH (not used in 1981) (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - 501a, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - 501a, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Other course related information, 1999-2012 (Box 17-18)
    - Macalester talks 3125-26, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Continuing Studies, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 39-41)
    - Zammito (Box 17, Folder 42,43)
    - 2nd Spinoza seminar W Gregory Kaplan, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - PHIL 598 Salman Khansaja F, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - AP European History Kulstad (Box 18, Folder 3,4)
    - Multimedia Ap Lecture (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - RUSP lecture: Internationalism for Lngs. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - PHIL 372 (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
  - PHIL 202, 1976-2012 (Box 18)
    - Lecture Notes 202b Hobbes-Hume (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Lecture Summaries (loose Kant satire) (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kulstad- MRD Typed Notes 202 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hop II lecture Notes (Kant- 20th C) Kulstad Phil 202b (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 202 Final examinations midsemester and final, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - 202b Course Mtl a model packet, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Storage Overview Sheet and day by day outlines, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Syallabus + Student list, 1981-2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - 2026, day by day records, 1977-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Handouts, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Old lecture mtl (no longer in use) (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Midsems (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - HOP II, Handouts File: Current Masters (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Essay Q's, data on difficulty (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Overheads (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Kulstad Phil 202 tests intial handouts, thru Spinoza (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Handouts (Box 18, Folder 26,27)
    - Phil 202 HO Masters', 2008 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Spring? Phil 202, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Internet Readings (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Phil 202, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Phil 202, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Phil 202, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Spring Phil 202, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - 502 and 501a, 1983-1993 (Box 18-19)
    - 502a Modern Descartes (esp. circle) (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Phil 501a, readings Leibniz student copies, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Alexander Boyle and Locke on Qualities Tipton pp. 77 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Boyle selected phil papers M.A. Stewart assorted pages (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Leibniz on the elements of natural science- Loemker p. 277 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Descartes Discourse on Method Cottingham pp. 126- 131 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Leibniz "Brief Demonstration" (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Leibniz New System Loemker (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Leibniz "Principles of Nature and of Grace" (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Leibniz Monadology Loemker (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - M.D. Wilson "Leibniz is Dynamics and Contingency in Nature" (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - "First Truths", circa 1680-1684 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Burtt, The Metaphysical Foundations (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Galileo by Stillman Drake intro (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Locke, "View of the Essay", BK IV (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Garber Semel in Vita Rorty: Essays on Descartes Mediations (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Descartes Principles of Philosophy Cottingham (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Newton's Philosophy of Nature (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Leibniz, letter to Bourget, 1715-08-05 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Leibniz- Clarke Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Sp + Lebniz Articles: Summer / Phil 502 Supplementary Articles for 502, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - C.D. Broad "Leibniz's Last Controversy with the Newtonians" (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Leibniz- Clarke Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - M.R. ayers Ideas of Power and Substance Tipton (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Laudan Nature and Source of Locke on Hyptheses Tipton (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Locke Book II, Essay and III (Box 19, Folder 13,14)
    - 502 paper and drafts (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Phil 502 Master Copies, Phil 502 readings (Kulstad) Causation Mind-body (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Phil 502(Master copies) (Box 19, Folder 17,18)
    - Readings in for 501a Seminar in Modern Phil. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Jolley Leibniz and LK Sbst in Lk, Lz (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - M.R. Ayers, Peter Alexander, Ruth Mattern (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Articles on Locke and for Lz (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Phil 502 Fall, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Cartesian Circle Papers ( and Locke on personal identity) (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Spinoza (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Articles on Spinoza and Leibniz and his actual writing (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Phil 502 Desumma Rerum (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Hume Treatise Idea of Nec Comm (Core pages) (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Non- Sleigh, Non Leibniz readings for Sleigh 502/ 502, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Mondadori (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Hume Bricke, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Leibniz; and Leibniz and Arnauld a commentary (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - 501a Leibniz Readings: my copies ( old Leibniz version) (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Phil 302 Hume + Kant Modern Philosophy Spring (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Courses Mark Kulstad audited, 1976-2014 (Box 19-20)
    - Metaphysics graduate course, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Phil 512 Peacocke +Parfit Spring, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - 502 papers, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Engelhardts Kant seminar, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Phil 502a Bill Schmitz Greats (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Schmitz Phil of Lang Rdgs, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - 502 News, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Spinoza + Hume, Independent Study Richard Reilly + Nancy Hogan, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 502 Fall Early Modern Survey Great Topics, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 502 Newsletter Color, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Greg Brown, Adams Sem, F UH, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Course MH (from others mostly audits) De Rose, Phil 503, 1997-11-10 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Phil 502 Loeb Carlin, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Phil 502 Spring D,S, LK, LZ, H,K, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Course MH from others (mostly audits) other's syallabi (Rice), circa 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Phil 502 Fall Lz and Sp, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - 502 Greats, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 502/302 LK and LZ, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Spinoza Seminar Spring F2p w/ Gregory/ Kaplan Phil 390, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Phil 303 (Box 20, Folder 15-26)
    - Morrison Anc Phil Spring, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - 202, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Papers from C. Kirwan crs paper + profession (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Course MH from others mostly audits other's syallabi (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous courses and teaching evaluations, 1976-2013 (Box 20)
    - Phil 106c Summer school Logic tests, inference rules, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Phil 106 Logic Notes, Syallabus, Tests, 4-5 Summer, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Phil 106c Summer Logic: Including tests syallabus, formed incompleteness proof and 2 xeroxed fragments, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Summer Logic Phil 106, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Phil 202b (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Phil 302, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Hand-written teaching evaluations, 1986-1997 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - New mid-semester evaluations, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - AP multimedia lecture evaluations (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Evaluation Phil 202 001 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Continuing Studies, teaching evaluations, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Mogens Laerke teaching evaluations Phil 502, 2004-04-23 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Handwritten teaching evaluations (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Quant and Qual, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Peter Zuk Independent Reading Course Pacific APA, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Unusual sets of evaluations, eg department evaluations 202, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Teaching Evaluations (Quantitative) (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Phil 106c M. Kulstad copi, I.M. Solutions to Symbolic Logic (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Phil 502 L.Stein book (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - General course material (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Lecture/ and 1 complete test set (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - 541 Logic Solutions SH 562 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence about a course (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Annotations and correspondence about tenure review
      - II. a language for analysis, notes by Mark (Box 20, Folder 54)
      - Arturo Munoz paper (Box 20, Folder 55)
      - Cover/ O'Leary- Hawthorne (Box 20, Folder 56)
      - Forthcoming in the Journal of Philosophical Cosmology, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 57)
      - Glen A. Hartz tenure review (Box 20, Folder 58)
      - J.A. Cover annotations by Kulstad (Box 20, Folder 59)
      - Tenure review correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 60)
      - Stephen Grover papers annotation by Mark (Box 20, Folder 61)
      - Christian Mercer: Leibniz's Metaphysics: Its Origins and Development Volume I (Box 20)
- Series V: Research, 1978-2007 (Box 21-23)
  - Grants, Reserves, and Publishers, 1978-2007 (Box 21-22)
    - ACLS application, 1978-02-23 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - NEH summer stipend, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Fulbright, Utrecht, 1981-07-06 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - University grants, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Grant application - Alexander Von Humbodt Stiftung, 1982-03-31 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Humanities summer research grant, 1983-05-02 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Humboldt Stiftung Mtl (post- 80), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - External grant information (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Summer seminar for school teachers, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Alex Von Humboldt Stiftung "Term", 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Trans-cooperative, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - NEH summer seminar, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - New travel grant policy, 2004-03-30 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Mellon research seminar, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Professor published and reserve; book buying (Box 21, Folder 15,16)
    - Reserve from book lists, professor published and reserve (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Textbook orders, professor published and reserve (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - John Bino volume (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Hackett (post-publication) (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Peter Lang (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Additional published material (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Philosophia (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Cambridge U. Press (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Kluwer Expo Book (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Phil 502 paper Leibniz- Spinoza submitted to Hp, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - SL "Q's about Expression Thesis" (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - HPQ Spimoni paper, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Phil Review (Rutherford review) (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Leibniz's Metaphysics: Its Origins and Development Volume II (Box 21)
    - Yovel reprint of Spimoni Ashcroft, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Goodin and Kulstad Rannes Leibniz and Lang Leibniz and Net Kinds (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Publisher correspondence (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Hackett and report central themes (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Revisions and drafts (Box 22-23)
      - Introduction to Apperception book for researchers, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Philosophia Verlag (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Abstracts (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Buenos Aires Apperception paper (to publish) (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Mark A. Kulstad Apperception book (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Do Only Rational Animals Apperceive? (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Philosophia Verlag/final changes, 1990-01-23 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Philosophia Verlag (personal) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Philsophia corrected gallerys (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Philsophia's corrections on Apperception Book (Box 22, Folder 14)